♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
We now return
to the All in the Family
and Modern Family
crossover episode.
Hello,
Mr. Bunker.
We brought
some hummus.
Oh, yeah, I knew
them two was hummus
the minute
they walked in the door.
Yay! A crossover always brings
out the best in each show!
It certainly doesn't smack
of desperation.
The priorities
are always creative,
and not driven
by marketing or...
Okay, that's
enough.
Oh, my God!
What is it, Peter?
Look at this. Dennis the Menace
is just shoveling snow.
He's being helpful.
Might as well just
call it Dennis now.
He's not a menace.
Not every strip
is gonna be hilarious.
You know something? I could
do better than these idiots.
I should just go down to
the paper and sell 'em my own.
Well, Peter, you might be
underestimating the difficulty
of writing a comic strip.
As someone who occasionally
dates the creative muse,
I can vouch for the unforgiving
face of a blank sheet of paper.
In fact, I think it was
William Faulkner who said...
I'm back. I'm published.
Check it out.
I call my comic
For Pete's Sake,
because it points out things
that make you shake your head
and say, "For Pete's sake."
This one's for tomorrow.
These are
good, Peter.
I like how
you retell tired old gags
with a detached,
ironic approach.
Yeah, plus,
it's all brand-new jokes
that I'm really,
really serious about.
Well, good for you, Peter,
but how did you get published
so quickly?
Ah, the editor of the paper
owed me a favor.
I got him a picture
of Spider-Man.
Why can't anyone get me
a picture of the Spider-Man?!
Here you go.
Yeah, I got a whole subreddit
of superhero thong shots.
Here's your beer, Peter.
Thanks, Jerome.
What do I owe you?
Nah, you already
paid me... in laughs.
I do a lot of island ones.
Peter, you
should do one
where a baseball player
can't steal second,
'cause he's
on probation.
For drug crimes.
Political.
Yeah, you put an island
in there, you're in business.
Hey, how about one
where you draw a sock,
and it says "Sock it to me,"
or-or maybe draw Lois
taking a hot-tub dump,
and she just says whatever?
Peter, your comic
in this morning's paper
is really offensive.
That's not funny, Peter.
Ah, you're just not
getting it, Lois.
See, his wife washed
dishes for him.
Oh, for Pete's sake.
Aha! There you go.
Peter, you should see this.
Your dishwasher cartoon
has really outraged
the online community.
What?
Gosh, it's not
like the Internet
to go crazy about something
small and stupid.
Peter, you have
to apologize.
What, because of a joke?
Not just a joke, Peter.
A joke that angered some bloggers.
Well, I guess this
ain't the first time
I got in trouble for something
I said about a woman.
Oh, good.
We can steal.
And welcome back
to The Flow.
We're talking
to Peter Griffin,
the artist behind
For Pete's Sake,
which has caused outrage
with a misogynistic comic.
Here's a video
of some outrage.
Boo!
Yeah, those boos
don't hurt so much
'cause you spent two minutes
of the last segment
applauding a red velvet cake.
Ah!
And if that's not bad enough,
this morning's cartoon
is even worse.
Let's put that up.
Mr. Griffin,
do you really think
this is an
appropriate cartoon
to run on Gloria Steinem's
half-birthday?
You sound angry.
Did one of your
friends get engaged?
You have no idea how offensive
you are to women, do you?
What?! I love women.
I bet I can name more
porn stars than you.
But-but don't tell my wife
how many porn stars I know.
I'll get in a
lot of trouble.
I know all of
'em, though.
There are people
who just started an hour
ago, and I know 'em.
Your cartoon is sexist!
Down with misogyny!
It wasn't even funny, and
I have a great sense of humor.
Man, they seem really upset.
I was just trying
to make people laugh.
Dad, I'm worried
they're gonna hurt us.
No, no,
they're angry, Chris,
but they ain't
gonna get violent.
Oh, cool!
That brick I ordered.
Wait a minute.
I didn't order this brick.
You may be right, Chris.
Peter, this is
getting out of hand.
I don't feel safe
in my own home.
Maybe we should get out
of Quahog for a while.
You know, she's right.
We should get out of town
till this all blows over.
Okay, we'll go,
but just give me a minute.
I just want to turn in
my last For Pete's Sake.
going out on top amid a flurry
of gambling rumors.
Peter, where are we?
I don't know.
I just woke up, too.
I tied the steering
wheel to my belt.
I figure we've been on the
road about 20% of the time.
Dad, how long
until we can go back home?
Um, I don't know.
How long do women
hold grudges?
Not very long,
I'm guessing.
Oh, Peter, we've been
driving all night.
Pull over
to that gas station.
We can use the bathroom
and stretch our legs.
You got it, babe.
Did you call me "babe"?
I did.
Oh, Peter.
Ew! Mom!
You'll never
have this, Meg.
All right, back
in the car, kids.
For this leg of the
trip, I was thinking
of driving with my shirt
off like New Mexico trash.
Oh, my God!
Our car!
Someone's stealing it.
Ah, crap.
Although, I got to say,
you never get to see
somebody else driving your car.
It's kind of cool.
Kind of weird.
We're stuck
here, Peter!
And we don't even
know where we are.
Well, there's a sign.
Huh, guess we're in a town
called Springfield.
Springfield, eh?
What state?
I can't imagine
we're allowed to say.
Well, this Springfield place
seems nice.
We should visit here again.
I don't know, Lois. This
seems like a one-shot deal.
Guys, we ain't here
for fun, all right?
We're here to find the police,
report our stolen car.
Oh, and don't
drink the water.
Everybody around here looks
like they have hepatitis.
Dad, I'm
starving.
Can we get
some food?!
Lois, whip out your boob,
give the boy his lunch.
Listen to
the man.
Yeah, Lois,
listen to the man.
How about we just go into
that store there?
Uh, uh, excuse me?
Hello. Welcome
to the Kwik-E-Mart.
Oh, I am so sorry.
Let me unplug that.
Oh, such a nuisance!
Hello, funny-sounding
Cleveland.
What's the specialty
of the house?
To you, I recommend...
the donut.
Ooh!
Yum!
Have you guys seriously
never heard of donuts?
These are made
fresh every day.
And then, several days
later, we receive them
and make them available
for purchase.
Hey, are these...
are these free?
'Cause I forgot to mention, all
our money is in our stolen car.
Thank you. Come again.
Sir, we can pay you back for
the donuts when we find our car.
Do you think that I am moved
by your sob story?
I come from a country
where the words
for "sewage" and "beverage"
are the same.
I'll pay for their donuts.
Thank you so
much, sir.
For what?
I didn't say anything.
Oh.
It was me.
How come this convenience store
has so many shadowy parts?
Apu, a dozen donuts for
our albino visitors.
Wow! For real?!
No man should be so poor
he cannot pay for a donut.
I was once you.
I couldn't afford donuts.
Tell them what I did, Apu.
He stole the donuts.
I stole the donuts.
So, here you go.
12... ten...
eight donuts.
That's very nice
of you, Mister...?
Simpson. Homer Simpson.
We're the Griffins.
Peter, Lois, Stewie, and then,
uh, you know, the others.
Brian, I guess.
Well, enjoy
your... six donuts.
Mmm. Yummy... donut.
That's pretty good,
but try it like this.
Mmm. Donut.
I think you and I are
gonna get along just okay.
Yeah, all right,
we'll be there.
But if you want
to save us a little time,
you can start
tracing his body with chalk.
This is the
police station.
Be careful. I think some
of them might be cops.
Oh, hey there.
Cool hat, weird nose.
Hey, listen,
my car got stolen.
I was hoping
you could help.
Well, we got
a procedure
for handling alleged
crimes around here.
Let's see. Uh, did
you contribute
to the policeman's ball?
No.
Oh, that's too bad,
'cause he really needs one.
He had an accident last week.
Yeah, I tried to jump
over a parking meter.
Yeah, all right,
well, with no contribution,
your report goes right
into the circular file.
I got to be honest.
I don't usually check this file,
so it might be a while
until we find that car of yours.
Uh, Chief, that excuse to
leave you asked for is here.
Oh, sorry,
I got to take this.
It never ends.
Oh, thank you so much
for putting us up
until we find our car.
And thank you for not being
a band of hippie murderers.
And now
this again.
You bring home two bands
of hippie murderers,
and suddenly,
that's all you're about.
Well, what do you say we have
some lunch?
Where's
Bart?
Well, he's at
camp all week.
I'm sorry you
won't get to meet him.
Got kicked out of camp.
I superglued my counselor's
butt cheeks together.
That's terrible.
But how did you even get access
to his butt cheeks?
I'm not the only one
who got kicked out of camp.
This is Bart.
Honey, your hands
are filthy.
Go wash up
for lunch.
Eat my shorts!
"Eat my shorts."
I love that!
Is that a popular expression,
like "what the deuce"?
Probably more popular.
Probably... probably
way more popular.
Well, here's my room.
Hey, you want to see
my weapons closet?
You have a
weapons closet, too?
Ouch! Jesus
heard my mean thought!
A slingshot!
It's so simple and pure.
He doesn't need lasers
or time machines,
just gum balls and marbles
and balls of string.
He's like something
out of Mark Twain!
Whose real name
was Samuel Clemens.
How... how does that further
this conversation?
Hey, you want to make
a prank phone call?
Ooh, prank phone call!
Moe's Tavern.
Moe speaking.
Uh, yeah, I'm looking
for a friend,
last name Keebum,
first name Lee.
Uh, hang on, I'll check.
Hey, guys, do I got
a Lee Keebum?
Come on, look at the stools--
is there a Lee Keebum?
Somebody check the rear--
I know I got a Lee Keebum.
Then you probably shouldn't
be handling food.
Oh, my God,
that's amazing!
That's the coolest
thing ever!
Hey, I want to try.
Okay.
Moe's Tavern.
Hello, Moe?
Your sister's being raped.
Is that... is that one?
So, this is my room.
Please excuse the mess.
There, that's better.
Look at all these trophies!
There must be,
like, 20 of them!
23. But I'm sure you have
a lot of trophies of your own.
No. I'm not good
at anything.
Oh, Meg, I'm sure
you're good at something.
We just have
to find out what it is.
After all, Nelson Mandela said
it's our obligation to shine.
You mean like my
oily face and back?
No. Maybe don't sit
on my bedspread, please.
But I mean the light within you
that makes you an individual.
Meg, you need to know
that you matter.
Really? No one's ever
told me I mattered before.
That's why you
have to say it.
So say it.
I matter.
Louder!
I matter!
Shut up, Meg! You don't matter!
Hey, couldn't help but notice
there's no seat for me.
Oh. I was under the impression
that you were a dog.
You're right to have
that reaction, Marge.
Why, I just figured,
at home I sit with the family,
so I assumed that...
Have you ever drunk
out of a toilet?
I-I don't see what that has
to do with the discussion.
Dogs eat in the kitchen.
Yeah, dogs eat
in the kitchen.
Y-You know, you're eating
mostly horse hooves
and tallow, right?
You cool with that?
Oh, and the ones that
fall on the floor,
you just eat those
up, too, huh?
Oh, yeah, yeah, you do.
So, is that... is that,
like, your thing?
You eat loud?
I... I'm-I'm sorry,
I don't know what...
That's a gutter language.
Are you making friends
in there, Brian?
Yep, he's a lot
of laughs.
Wow, you work at a
nuclear power plant?
What's that?
I don't know.
Pretty impressive.
I just work
at a brewery.
Oh, my God,
you get to work with beer?!
Wow! What's beer really like?
Eh, he's got a big head.
Hey, you know-- aw, damn it,
I don't have a comic strip anymore.
So, still no word from the
police on your stolen car?
The cops
here are a joke.
I bet you and me can find
your car on our own.
You think so?
Yeah.
'Cause Homer Simpson
and Peter Griffin
are a great team!
A greater team than...
Than...
Uh-huh, keep going.
Than... something else.
Something else?
I... don't know what this is.
O-Okay,
I'll do it.
Homer Simpson and Peter Griffin
are an even greater team
than the Air Force!
Hold steady.
I got him in my sights.
Whoo-hoo!
Yeah-heh-heh!
Yeah, we did it.
What's he doing here?
We got to carry him,
'cause he can't fly on his own.
We let that other guy try,
and look what happened.
No, no, no, no, no, no...!
Wow, they've made a lot
of changes to Quahog!
Chris, we're
in a different town.
Oh...
Is that why there was
blood in my stool?
No. That-that sounds
like a separate issue.
God, I can't believe
I got stuck
taking their stupid dog
for a walk.
Stupid? Well, I don't know,
I think he's kind of fun.
What, are you kidding?
He doesn't do anything.
You know,
it's not his fault, though.
He doesn't know any better.
He's been on a leash
his whole life.
Hey, you know what?
Come here, Santa's Stupid Name.
You're a grown dog--
start acting like one.
Come here, boy.
Hey, stop that dog!
Sorry. We're
on a smoke break.
Nothing beats
smoking and standing.
Although smoking and sitting
does have its moments.
You always have
to argue with me.
Oh, thank goodness!
I was starting to think
you wouldn't show, Dr. Dog.
Boy, you really like
to bleed, huh, guy?
Hey, there's a dog
in the dining area!
How'd that happen?
Get back in there.
Which one is Santa's
Little Helper?
I don't know. You're the one who
sniffed his butt.
Yeah, for, like,
a second!
Damn it, he's gone.
We're screwed.
Welcome to Krusty Burger.
May I take your order?
Your voice
sounds stupid.
Oh, my God,
that was great!
I mean, unless you think it sucked,
in which case it sucked.
It was all right, dude.
Yeah, dude.
So, you know, um,
I'm only wearing this diaper
as a dare, you know-- it's not,
like, an everyday thing.
Hey, loser, I copied
off your spelling test
and got a D!
Haw-haw!
I say, how long has that boy
been treating you like that?
Uh...
about 24 years.
Aah!
Just who I was
looking for!
Cowabunga.
All right, Peter, if we're
gonna find your car,
we got to think
like a car.
So let's fill up
at that gas station.
I feel sick.
Keep drinking.
I prepaid 40 bucks!
Homer, maybe
we're doing this wrong.
Oh, crap.
Haben Sie Homer und
Peter MIT Chevron pump?
Okay, I got a great idea how
we're gonna find my stolen car.
We'll throw a car wash--
free for stolen cars!
And then when we find it,
we'll actually charge the guy!
Well, none of these
is my car,
but we promised
these scumbags a show.
♪ Love is like a bomb, baby,
come on, get it on ♪
♪ Livin' like a lover
with a radar phone ♪
♪ Lookin' like a tramp,
like a video vamp ♪
♪ Demolition woman,
can I be your man? ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ So come on, take a bottle ♪
♪ Shake it up ♪
♪ Break the bubble ♪
♪ Break it up ♪
♪ Pour some ♪
♪ Sugar on me ♪
♪ Ooh, in the name of love ♪
♪ Pour some ♪
♪ Sugar on me ♪
♪ Come on, fire me up ♪
♪ Pour your ♪
♪ Sugar on me ♪
♪ I can't get enough... ♪
Hey, Chief, we could arrest every single
car thief in Springfield.
After the show, Lou,
after the show.
I don't know!
I feel like I'm good at nothing!
Hey, everyone gets down
on themselves sometimes.
Those are the days
I'm glad I have my saxophone.
Saxophone?
Yeah. My dad
gave it to me.
My dad once gave me
a gun to hide.
That's terrible.
Whenever I feel
any pain or loneliness,
I just play away the blues
on my saxophone.
Huh. I usually
just beat up a cat.
Good thing we don't have a cat.
Why don't you
give it a shot?
Was that good?
It was okay, but it would
be a shame to waste
such great butcher's arms
on a musical instrument.
Wakey, wakey.
Good morning.
You and I have quite a day
ahead of us.
Oh, that's a clown I painted,
so you know I'm truly insane.
You know, Nelson,
I don't doubt that you've
had a twisted childhood.
Most evil people have.
Hitler, Manson, Jaden Smith.
But you're different
from them, aren't you?
Because they're rail-thin,
and you're fat.
You're a little piggy,
aren't you, Nelson?
In fact, I bet
you're hungry right now.
What's that?
I could eat.
Good. Because you're going
to eat... my... shorts.
Homer, you're never going
to believe what we did.
We saw a movie
in the afternoon!
Yeah, we saw
Surf's Up 2.
Marge covered her eyes every
time the penguins surfed.
It made me nervous.
They could drown.
Hey, where's
Santa's Little Helper?
Brian, you took him
for a walk, right?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
More-more like he took me
for a walk.
God, what a...
what a fun dog.
He's in the kitchen right now,
totally accounted for.
Shut up.
I'll, uh... I'll go check
on him right now.
And Chris
will come with me.
But nobody else!
BRIAN
Ruff! Ruff, ruff!
Ah, there he is!
Aw, you like that
behind the ear, don't you, boy?
Ruff! Ruff, ruff!
Ruff, ruff! I'm
another dog in here!
What the hell are you doing?
He's having a
dog playdate.
How does that help us?
We're creating a broad story.
Also, Matthew McConaughey
is in here, too!
"All right, all right, all right."
No, no, he's-he's not
really in here! He's...
We-we thought it was him,
but it was just the oven!
Now you're just doing voices.
Jack Nicholson?!
Okay, Santa's Little Helper
got all tuckered out
from his playdate, so he went
out back to take a nap
under that tree where nobody
knows quite where it is.
Hey, what happened
to Jack Nicholson
and that other dog?
Yep.
Wait, aren't you supposed
to be looking for our car?
Didn't find the car, Lois,
but I found a good
time with a good pal.
Right, Homer? Hey,
Quagmire who, right?
Yeah, Quagmire who?
That's an actual question.
I don't know who Quagmire is.
Peter, I'm glad you made a
friend, but what about our car?
Yeah, I got an idea
about that.
What's the one surefire way
to find a lost car?
Giant magnet?
Giant magnet.
Check.
Giant plug?
Giant curbside outlet?
Oh, things never work
the way they do on the box.
Okay, let's get this garbage
out of the street.
Oh, dear, I was using that car
as pants.
Oh, my God, Dad,
it's our car!
That confused old guy must have
been driving it by mistake.
How many confused old guys
you got in this town?
I'm old, so I'm the victim!
Well, Homer, thanks
for helping me get my car back.
And to show my appreciation, I
got a little something for you.
Here you go.
Pawtucket Patriot Ale.
The best Quahog
has to offer.
Always keep an emergency
six-pack in my trunk.
Oh, that's cool, bringing
outside beer into my bar.
Down the hatch!
That's pretty good, right?
No.
Huh?
It's not good.
This beer tastes exactly
like Duff.
It's just a lousy rip-off.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's not a rip-off of Duff.
It may have been inspired
by Duff, but I-I like to think
it goes in
a different direction.
No, this is just the same
as Duff, but, like, worse.
Hey, come on, now, this is
my favorite beer you're talking about.
Hell, I work for the company.
It's my livelihood.
Oh, yeah? Well, your livelihood
is based on fraud.
Look at this.
Huh?
It is Duff.
Your beer is
in big trouble!
You can't just slap
a new label on something
and call it your own!
Well, maybe Duff should be
in trouble for,
you know,
not being that great.
Duff is an icon!
Yeah, but some folks
prefer Pawtucket Pat.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I-I used to love Duff when I was younger,
but I-I haven't even had it
in, like, 13 years.
Be that as it may,
I represent the Duff Brewery,
and you, sir,
as a representative
of Pawtucket Patriot Ale,
are being sued for intellectual
theft and patent infringement.
Aha! Intellectual theft!
What do you have to say
about that, Griffin?
D'oh!
The Pawtucket Patriot
Brewery being sued?
It's the largest employer
in Quahog, Peter.
A lot of people's jobs
are riding on this.
Yeah, I got a job for you
riding on something.
Peter!
Sorry! Sorry, Lois,
I'm-I'm tired
'cause we usually only do
these things for half an hour.
Simpson.
Griffin.
Nice day, isn't it?
A nice day for stabbing
a friend in the back.
Yeah, and a nice day for
bringing thieves to justice.
We're getting a
lot of compliments.
Yep, we're doing
something right.
Your Honor,
citizens of Springfield
and visitors from Quahog,
my client, the Duff Brewery,
is the victim of flagrant
intellectual theft.
I'm whispering in court
to look smart.
But it's not just the main Duff
recipe that's been plagiarized.
Several other Duff variations,
packages
and design elements
have been similarly infringed,
resulting again
and again in pale imitations,
chp coes,
clumsy counterfeits
and weak substitutions.
You like sex?
Eh.
I don't think
we're very similar.
You know why they got us
sitting next to each other.
Uh, 'cause we're the two
funniest guys in our towns?
Damn right.
I'm a Jewish clown.
Me, too.
Are you a mayor?
Yes, I am.
Are you a "cool" mayor?
I, uh... I like
to think so.
You lived in Springfield?
Yeah, I worked at the
Kwik-E-Mart, researching a role.
These guys are gonna lose.
I've heard all I need to
hear to make a decision.
If you ask me, neither of
these beers is wholly original.
They're both pale imitations
of my favorite beer, Bud Rock.
- Oh, ho, ho!
- Ooh!
But rendering a verdict
is something
I'm paid to yabba-dabba-do!
Eh.
And I find in favor of Duff.
Oh, no!
Hello?
Uh, hey.
I'm-I'm
in the wrong Springfield.
So what's going
to happen now?
Well, the Pawtucket Brewery
will be shut down,
so I guess we got to go back to
Quahog and find Peter a new job.
Mmm, that's too bad.
Yeah. Anyways, it was still nice
to meet you and your family,
even though you kind of
screwed us over.
Good to have you.
And, hey, next time
you stay with a family,
maybe you can wear a
bra some of the time.
Hey, uh, Marge, uh,
listen, there's something
difficult that I've been trying
to figure out how to
tell you, and, um...
it's about, uh,
Santa's Little Helper.
What about him?
He's, um...
...right there.
You were trying to figure out
a way to tell me that?
I overthink things
sometimes.
Oh, and, look,
he's with Ed McMahon!
Hey-o!
Here's Johnny!
Chris, we're done.
You may be, but...
"I'm just getting warmed up!"
That's Al Pacino.
Thanks for being
so cool, Lisa.
I cut your name in my arm
so I'll always remember you.
Meg, I want you to have this.
Your saxophone?
Yes, Meg.
When you played the saxophone,
Lisa, no one has ever done
anything this nice for me.
You're amazing,
and I will never be like you.
I'm not pretty, I'm not smart,
I'm not talented.
I have the same shoe size
as Charles Barkley.
My prom date
was a scarecrow I stole,
and he left
with someone else.
The inside of my hat
smells so bad I'm not allowed
in most restaurants...
Hey, hey!
Shut up, Meg.
No luggage. Car's full.
Let's go.
Well, nice knowing you,
Stewie.
Same here, Bart.
Hey, I hope
you don't mind,
I got you a
little present.
Whoa. Is that Nelson?
Stewie, what the deuce?
Yes, I... Oh!
Oh, that's nice.
You got that from me.
'Cause, you know,
I was starting to worry
this was a one-way thing.
You kidnapped him?
I kidnapped all your enemies.
Nelson, Jimbo, Principal
Skinner, Sideshow Bob, Apu.
I know Apu's not your enemy,
but I just wanted to say,
"I took Apu."
That is funny!
But the rest of this?
It's messed up, man.
I know! Isn't it awesome?
So, how do you want to keep
in touch? Facebook? Twitter?
Late-night phone calls
lying on our tummies
with our feet up in the air?
Stewie, I don't think
we can be friends.
You freak me out.
Bart, if we don't keep in touch,
I'll kill myself.
That's what I'm talking about.
Later, dude!
Later...
dude.
Haw-haw!
Aw.
Hey, Griffin.
Sorry about your job.
I was just sticking
up for Duff.
I love Duff.
And Duff loves me.
Duff can keep a secret.
Duff never says no.
Duff is more experimental than
any partner I've ever had.
Anyway, the point
is, I'm sorry.
You know, when I first met you,
I thought, hey, I love this guy!
This is the funniest guy
I've ever met.
I'm gonna quote this guy
to all my friends.
I love his town,
I love his family.
But now, I think
I speak for all of us
when I say,
I am over the Simpsons!
Wh-What
are you saying?
I'm saying
the Simpsons suck!
Why, you...
Ow! What the hell?
That really hurts.
No, it doesn't!
I do it to my son all the time.
You strangle your son?
That's insane!
No wonder he's fat and stupid
and masturbates all the time.
That's your son!
Phew!
Hey! Knock it off!
There's a kid back there!
I'm in danger.
Hey, that's no fair.
I don't got none of them.
Uh-oh.
Hey, hey!
Ooh.
Damn it!
And remember, kids,
TV violence is fine
as long as you
don't show a nipple.
Perfect.
The earthlings are
destroying themselves.
Yeah, it's really great,
isn't it, guys?
We went to summer camp together.
Bye! Thanks for having me.
Huh?
It appears that I
am now the only one
with radioactive powers,
which will allow me
to unleash my fury...
Oh, I talked too long.
- We're gonna make it!
- Trust me, we're not.
Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Whoa!
Whoo-hoo!
Road house.
Aah-aah!
Say hi to Maude Flanders.
No. You say hi
to Muriel Goldman.
Who?
What are you
still doing here?
I think you're gonna get
a kick out of this.
You're parked behind me
at your place.
That is funny.
Hey, listen, I...
I'm sorry we fought.
I just wanted
to make you laugh and cry.
You see, I'm a Family Guy.
I understand.
I'm a The Simpsons.
Look, even if we
don't work as best pals,
I respect you.
You, too.
Let's just agree to stay a half hour
away from each other.
With a pile of
garbage between us.
Worst chicken fight ever.
It sure is nice to
be back in Quahog.
Oh, and thank God all the commotion
about Dad's comic blew over.
Oh, my God, I had a comic?
That's hilarious!
Well, you may not be
a cartoonist anymore,
but you are a local hero
for defending our beer,
and apparently, that's more
important than hating women.
So here you go,
a Pawtucket Patriot Ale.
What? I don't understand.
Ain't the brewery out of business?
We lost a court case.
Yes, we lost,
but how are they
gonna enforce it?
What, are they
gonna come here?
I think we know that's
never gonna happen.
Hey, Stewie, I'm sorry Bart
didn't want to be your friend.
What? No! What are
you talking about?
He was lame.
If you ask me,
he kind of sounded like a girl.
Really?
Kind of seemed like
you idolized him.
And I can understand losing
a friend and feeling rejected.
Course you can!
You're a loser.
But not me.
I'm a lone wolf.
Speaking of which,
I'm gonna go howl at the moon.
Don't need nobody.
Shh.
♪ And now the show
is over now. ♪
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru